Hi my name is Mary Thinnes and I am a skin care expert.
Now I am going to discuss with you dehydrated skin and how to properly treat dehydrated skin.
Don't get confused because dehydrated skin is different from dry skin.
Dry skin is actually a skin type and dehydrated skin is a condition.
Dry skin is lacking in oil and dehydrated skin is lacking in water.
Not only does it have to do with properly hydrating your body with water just because someone drinks more water does not mean that their skin is going to actually be hydrated like they want to and have that healthy skin glow but you have to properly treat your skin as well.
With dehydrated skin you want to definitely do proper home care treatments, your masks on a bi-weekly basis, you want to break down your papayas to break down those dead skin cells because you don't want to get that surface build up but at the same time with dehydrated skin moisturizing is the most important step for them as well.
You definitely want to use more products with pure hyaluronic acid in it for more mature skin use the moisturizers that have the antioxidants in them and your vitamins in there.
Also your vitamin C serum, the specialty product I mentioned before is going to help with dehydrated skin to help tighten, brighten and lighten the skin.
As far as that goes that is the way to properly treat dehydrated skin.